LAUREN CRAMER

OVERVIEW

Graduate from UCI with a B.S. in Informatics and a specialization in HCI. 2+ years of management experience. 6+ years of technical support experience. Diversified skills including customer service, human resources, management, programming, graphic design, web design, and UI design.

CONTACT

310.413.4509 lcramer@uci.edu

EDUCATION

University of California, Irvine | Informatics

SEPT 2013 - JUNE 2019

» Specialization: Human-Computer Interaction

El Segundo High School

SEPT 2009 - JUNE 2013

SKILLS

Languages

 Java
 ● ● ● ○ ○

 Python
 ● ● ○ ○

 C/C++
 ● ● ○ ○

Design

Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
Sketch-Up

Web Dev

CONNECT

in Ircramer

(aurencramer

laurencramer.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Eskape Rooms | Operations Manager

FEB 2019 - PRESENT

- » Assess and integrate new business software.
- » Employee hiring and scheduling.
- » Track company finances and revenue.
- » Tech support on computers & room props.
- » Employee payroll.

Savage Enterprises | IT Manager

SEPT 2018 - FEB 2019

- » Systems & user troubleshooting.
- » Evaluate procedures & processes.
- » Preparing & evalutating workflow solutions.
- » Developing & maintaining systems.
- » Research & implement new software.

Savage Enterprises | Systems Analyst

JUNE 2018 - SEPT 2018

- » Systems & user troubleshooting.
- » Maintain & update systems.
- » Provide manuals for personnel.

Eskape Rooms | Manager

FEB 2017 - FEB 2018

- » Employee hiring and scheduling.
- » Track company finances and revenue.
- » Tech support on computers & room props.
- » Employee payroll.
- » Worked long hours to complete tasks.

Eskape Rooms | Game Master

AUG 2016 - FEB 2017

- » Assist customers in-person & over phone.
- » Handle customer complaints.

HelloTech | Tech Support

AUG 2015 - PRESENT

- » Travel to customers' homes.
- » Resolve various tech issues.
- » Explain solution to customers.
- » Teach customers error prevention.

Jack Nadel Int. | Temp Account Specialist

JUNE 2015 - AUG 2015

- » Assist clients with their sales orders.
- » Assist sales executives.